<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>tech-guide-en</title>
    <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en</link>
    <description>Tech Tutorials相关内容</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Web App: A Beginner-Friendly How to Build a Simple Web App with Python Flask Tutorial - how to build a simple web app with python flask tutorial</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/build-simple-web-app-python-flask-tutorial/</link>
      <description>Learn how to build a simple web app with Python Flask! This tutorial guides you through setup, routing, templates, and more – perfect for beginners.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:13:13.600930</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash Your Inner Writer: The Best Free AI Tools for Content Creation in 2024 - best free ai tools for content creation 2024</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/best-free-ai-tools-for-content-creation-2024/</link>
      <description>Struggling with content creation? Discover the best free AI tools in 2024 to write blog posts, articles, and more – boost your SEO & save time!</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:13:52.325936</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Home Office: The Ultimate Cybersecurity Basics for Remote Workers Checklist - cybersecurity basics for remote workers checklist</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/cybersecurity-basics-remote-workers-checklist/</link>
      <description>Remote work offers flexibility, but also new security risks. This cybersecurity basics for remote workers checklist helps you protect your data & devices.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:14:33.654735</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming Tutorial for Data Analysis Beginners: From Zero to Insights - python programming tutorial for data analysis beginners</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/python-programming-tutorial-data-analysis-beginners/</link>
      <description>Learn data analysis with Python! This tutorial guides beginners through the essentials, from setup to data visualization. Start your data science journe...</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:57:14.235310</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best AI Tools for Content Creation 2024: A Tech-Guide-En Deep Dive - best AI tools for content creation 2024</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/best-ai-tools-for-content-creation-2024/</link>
      <description>Struggling with content creation? Discover the best AI tools for content creation in 2024 to boost your workflow, generate ideas, and write compelling c...</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:57:57.300033</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Responsive Web Design with CSS: 10 Practical Tips for 2024 - web development tips for responsive design with CSS</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/responsive-web-design-css-tips/</link>
      <description>Learn essential web development tips for responsive design with CSS. Create websites that look great on any device! Practical guide for developers.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:58:41.092789</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Basics for Small Business Owners: A Simple Guide to Protecting Your Livelihood - cybersecurity basics for small business owners</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/cybersecurity-basics-for-small-business-owners/</link>
      <description>Protect your small business from cyber threats! Learn essential cybersecurity basics, practical steps, and affordable solutions in this easy-to-understa...</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T04:59:27.074052</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Your Potential: A Productivity Apps Review for Students with ADHD - productivity apps review for students with ADHD</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/productivity-apps-review-students-adhd/</link>
      <description>Struggling with focus? This productivity apps review for students with ADHD offers practical tools & strategies to manage time, tasks, and stay on track!</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T05:00:19.566578</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Learn Coding for Beginners with No Experience: Your Step-by-Step Guide - how to learn coding for beginners with no experience</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/how-to-learn-coding-for-beginners/</link>
      <description>Want to learn to code but don't know where to start? This guide breaks down how to learn coding for beginners with no experience, offering resources & a...</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T05:01:06.285602</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Multi-Factor Authentication and How to Enable It: A Complete Guide to Protecting Your Digital Life - what is multi-factor authentication and how to enable it</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/what-is-multi-factor-authentication-and-how-to-enable-it/</link>
      <description>Learn what multi-factor authentication (MFA) is and how to enable it on your accounts. Protect yourself from hackers with this easy-to-follow guide!</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T05:01:54.134624</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding for Beginners: Python Projects with Step-by-Step Instructions to Ignite Your Skills - coding for beginners python projects with step-by-step instructions</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/coding-for-beginners-python-projects/</link>
      <description>Learn Python through hands-on projects! This guide offers coding for beginners with step-by-step instructions, perfect for starting your programming jou...</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T05:02:43.462112</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Computing Basics: AWS vs Azure vs Google Cloud – Which is Right for You? - cloud computing basics AWS vs Azure vs Google Cloud</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/cloud-computing-basics-aws-vs-azure-vs-google-cloud/</link>
      <description>Demystifying cloud computing! Learn the basics of AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud, their strengths, and how to choose the best platform for your needs.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T16:37:33.560237</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Data Science Tutorial with Python Examples? A Beginner's Guide to Unlocking Insights - what is data science tutorial with python examples</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/what-is-data-science-tutorial-with-python-examples/</link>
      <description>Learn data science with Python! This tutorial covers the basics, key tools, and practical examples to get you started. Unlock data insights today!</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-26T16:38:14.618600</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Hero: Your Complete Python Programming Tutorial for Beginners - Python programming tutorial</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/python-programming-tutorial-beginners/</link>
      <description>Learn Python programming with our beginner-friendly tutorial! Covers syntax, data types, control flow, functions & more. Start coding today!</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T02:13:08.278909</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate AI Tools Guide: Boost Your Productivity & Unlock New Possibilities in 2024 - AI tools guide</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/ultimate-ai-tools-guide/</link>
      <description>Confused about AI? This comprehensive AI tools guide breaks down the best AI software for productivity, content creation, and more. Start leveraging AI ...</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T02:13:51.489943</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 Essential Web Development Tips to Build Faster, Better Websites in 2024 - web development tips</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/essential-web-development-tips-2024/</link>
      <description>Boost your web development skills! Discover 25 practical web development tips for cleaner code, faster loading times, and a better user experience.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T02:14:33.848497</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Basics: A Beginner's Guide to Staying Safe Online in 2024 - cybersecurity basics</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/cybersecurity-basics-beginners-guide/</link>
      <description>Learn essential cybersecurity basics to protect your data, devices, and identity online. Simple steps for beginners to enhance their digital security.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T02:15:18.972951</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to productivity apps review</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/productivity-apps-review/</link>
      <description>Learn everything about productivity apps review with practical tips and expert advice.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T06:06:04.048549</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to coding for beginners</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/coding-for-beginners/</link>
      <description>Learn everything about coding for beginners with practical tips and expert advice.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T06:06:10.155634</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to cloud computing basics</title>
      <link>https://bigsea668.github.io/tech-guide-en/cloud-computing-basics/</link>
      <description>Learn everything about cloud computing basics with practical tips and expert advice.</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-27T06:07:24.502145</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>